HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Security Chief M.Taggart

[align left, indent 25]
We would like to notify you that on 14th of October, 30km south of Dankas, a Search & Rescue Team found Worthington’s delivery group shuttle No.1356777KE crashed. The delivery group's remains and the cargo were recovered from the site. 

The initial investigation suggests the flight stabiliser's malfunction as a possible reason for the shuttle crash. A special commission was assembled at the initiative of the NSola coordinating council. Sabotage is possible.

In relation to Worthington’s delivery group's death and Research Group Chief Creighton’s death preceding it, the rival company attack should be considered highly probable. The hazard level is recommended to be raised up to the 3rd.

Shansky’s delivery group has been placed under your command to replace Worthington’s group. The dossier is attached. 


[align right]
NSola Coordinator I.Hurrigan