HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Autopsy report No.2007

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Based on the post-mortem examination of R.Dorian’s corpse, the submitted documents data and additional means of research has concluded:

[left 50, indent 0]
1. Dorian’s death is attributed to closed thoracic injuries.

2. The evidence we received from the autopsy:

[left 100]
a) four broken ribs and a massive thoracic hematoma.

b) widespread internal hemorrhaging as a result of the wounds suffered.

[left 50]
3. In terms of the injuries sustained, it is concluded that the victim’s multiple thoracic area trauma was inflicted by a fan blade that resulted in his death.

[left 0, align right]
Pathologist S.Perlmutter