HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Psychiatrist P.Jane

[align left, indent 25]
Regarding your medical report of engineer Strauss’s obsessive thoughts about one of the items I have to respond the following:

We don’t have any employees of the cerebral diagnostic competency equal to Strauss at the moment. He is irreplaceable.

Solve the problem with medication.

[indent 0, align right]
Executive Chief J.Dekker