HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Technical Chief I.Freeman

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Report of the anchor accident aftermath

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
The sequence of the events:

[left 50, indent 0]
18:35 Shift on duty detected a detonation at the anchor cooling system.

18:40 Peak output power jumped to 5000 MG with a feedback of 4.5. Adding stabilizers to the active zone reduces the feedback to 3.2, but the peak output never drops under 5000 MG. 

18:42 Technical service staff were raised by alarm by the Shift Supervisor's decision.

18:44 Central core stabilization system failure and a subsequent entropic flash of 18GHn were detected.

18:53 Technical service managed to shut down the central core with a reverse current. 

18:55 Emergency power supply was activated.

[left 0, indent 25]
As at 20:30

[left 50, indent 0]
1. After examining the main systems of the central and auxiliary cores, it was an concluded that the cause of the detonation was an explosive device placed under coolant lines.

2. Central core is critical. Stabilization system is malfunctioning. Cooling system is significantly damaged, coolant leak is observed.

3. Anchor restart using the auxiliary core is impossible owing to the stability system's extensive damage. Core membrane melting, entropic cascade and a secondary flash of 50 GHn are highly possible.

4. Entropy level is critical, doesn’t go lower than 5200 Hnph. The staff are showing signs of the 2nd and 3rd stages of entromutation. Immediate evac required. Alert systems activated. 

[left 0, align right]
Senior Technician L.Gasoff