HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Report of Straus’s interrogation in relation to the accident on September 23rd

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
On September 23rd, engineer Strauss came to the private zone where he had a conflict with security officer Veinheid. During the interrogation engineer Strauss stated that Veinheid took his botty so they got in a fight. He considers Veinheid responsible for the situation. 

Taking into account the fact that engineer Strauss was involved in such an incident for the first time and Engineering Chief P.Richard’s recommendation, it was decided to let him off with a warning. 

[align right]
Lieutenant M.Kane