HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Engineering Chief P.Richard

[align left, indent 25]
All of Skinner’s items have learning defects. According to the Martin-Tsunayoshi test they’re no higher than 10. None of them can be injected, it’s necessary to repeat the migration. Please, take appropriate measures, as we have a shutdown.

[align right]
Projection Chief Engineer С.Mulder