HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Engineering Chief P.Richard

[align left, indent 25]
In the morning when turning on duty, I found some evidence of vandalism in the injection section. Particularly, the HD535 item exposed to desecration was found at engineer Lorentz’s workplace.

5 probes of different diameter were removed from the item’s genitalia. The further exploitation is impossible due to the damage suffered. I request to take sanctions against engineer Lorentz and recover the cost of damage from him.

[align right]
Injection Engineer H.Sullivan