HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Medical report based on engineer Strauss’s psychiatric examination

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Engineer Strauss was sent for a psychiatric examination because of numerous complaints, such as:

[left 50, indent 0]
1. Nervousness and persistent conflicts with his colleagues.
2. Violation of the private zone rules (personally trimmed a botty).
3. Fight with security officer Veinheid.
4. Falling productivity.

[left 0, indent 25]
Diagnostic measures taken:

[left 50, indent 0]
1. Examination of engineer Strauss’s file and interviewing colleagues.
2. Personal interview with engineer Strauss in a calm atmosphere.
3. Tetcher’s multifactorial questioning.

[left 0, indent 25]
The research findings:

The patient demonstrates the features of the 2nd stage of entropic refraction (entromutation). Obviously his dominating fixation is the HD512 item, which was confirmed by the patient himself during the interviews. For some reason Strauss distinguishes this item as unique, having its own will and place in the world. Multiple visits exclusively to the given item in the private zone support the former assumption.

Apparently, the fixation arose due to the patient's inability to “fix” the item defects during the diagnostic research. Other needs are clearly regressing.

Recommendations:

It is highly recommended to suspend engineer Strauss from duty due to the high risk of injury to himself and others, and immediately refer him for treatment. His continued presence at the facility is fraught with the inevitable move into the 3rd stage of entromutation.

[align right]
Psychiatrist P.Jane