HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Instruction for a technician 

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Recently there have been increasing incidents of B-234 substance leak. This substance is of high danger for the staff.

In case of leak detection the neutralizing agent (fluracynthreol) is to be injected to the air filtration system. Emergency filtration is activated automatically.

Contact the laboratory to restock the fluracyntreol.

[align right]
Technical Chief I.Freeman