HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right, indent 25]
To Engineering Chief P.Richard

[align center, font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20]
Explanatory

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
As a result of engineer Wolf’s death, and me not having any experience of the migration equipment settings, a number of errors were made. So the operation on a number of items was carried out incorrectly. 

Please, take my inexperience into account and give me some more time to set the equipment. 

[align right]
Acting Migration Engineer W.Skinner



