HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Commandant J.Lewis

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Complaint

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
To take out any objects imaginable out of the gallery mannequins, clean them and reset -  that’s what I do at the beginning of every shift. For the past month I’ve collected two buckets of stationery, a set of bottles, about a dozen engineering probes, a collection of beer cans and a full toolbox. I didn’t join up to do such work. Make the administrative stuff put an end to this nonsense or give me a raise. Until then, consider me resigned.

P.S. If someone on the stuff wants to get back anything listed above they’re free to buy it out.

[left 0, align right, indent 0]
Janitor P.Lein