HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Aether therapy memo

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left]
Tolerable presence period under entropic exposure:

[left 50]
0-100 Hnph - harmless

100-500 Hnph - normal level of the facility, presence period - a month

1000-2000 Hnph - no more than 24h provided with the 1st level protective equipment

2000-4000 Hnph - no more than 1h provided with the 3rd level protective equipment

>4000 Hnph - presence is unacceptable 

[left 0]
Entropic mutation stages

[left 50]
1. Expression of entropic refraction, light occupation fixation.

2. Clear expression of entropic refraction, strong occupation fixation, non-critical respiratory system malfunction.

3. Reversible appearance changes, severe entropic refraction, multiple failures of life support systems are possible.

4. Irreversible appearance changes, personality disintegration. 

[align right]
Senior technician L.Gasoff