HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Engineering Chief P.Richard

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Report of an HD512 item diagnostic research

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
HD512 was received from Mulder a week ago. The problem is the mimic resonance absence in spite of a high score according to Martin-Tsunayoshi. The injection and motorics rates are normal, but still she demonstrates a pokerface (in layman’s terms). They don’t understand what's going on, but I’ll explain: they make too much fuss about such a basic test as Martin-Tsunayoshi’s one. They don’t use other tests, as they’re likely not taught to. Meanwhile she has no more than 7 according to Deckard.

Her facial expressions are obviously controlled by a cognitive loop separated from the main cluster. We need a creative solution, as it’s impossible to reach this loop using conventional means. Unfortunately, by the moment it hasn’t been found. 

Though Mulder should’ve known that Martin-Tsunayoshi’s test doesn’t indicate such loops, the number of items like that shipped by his buttheads is still uncertain as well as cognitive clusters they’re able to control. And it makes the problem even worse. So I request that you give me more time for work, as this problem may have long-term consequences for the entire line-up.

[align right]
Diagnostic Engineer J.Strauss