HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Report of S.Lorentz’s interrogation

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
On 16th of October, the Engineering Department complained about engineer Lorentz’s disorderly conduct. During the apprehension the further search found a large quantity of drugs presumably missing from the medical storage at Lorentz’s workplace.

In the course of the interrogation engineer Lorentz pointed to Dr. Dorian as the one who had sold him the medication. It’s necessary to apprehend Dr.Dorian for questioning.  

[align right]
Detective A.Jensen