HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Executive Chief J.Dekker

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Brief report of HD512 diagnostic research results

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
In the course of the initial diagnostic research carried out at the stage of the item training, diagnostic engineer Strauss discovered a secondary cognitive loop, controlling the mimic. He had failed to neutralize that loop by conventional means so the item was decommissioned and transferred to the private zone. 

After the accident and subsequent Strauss’s arrest as an accomplice, at my initiative engineer Popper undertook a restudy.

The results of the initial research were confirmed. The item indeed has a cognitive loop, however its influence has recently spread. It’s impossible to determine if it happened as a result of Strauss’s actions, or natural causes.

Strauss’s initial assumption about potentially existing similar loops among the transported items makes sense. Further research of the item using our equipment isn’t possible.

Detailed report is attached.

[align right]
Engineering Chief P.Richard