HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Autopsy report No.1956

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Based on the post-mortem examination of J.Strauss’s corpse, the submitted documents data and additional means of research has concluded:

[left 50, indent 0]
1. Strauss’s death is attributed to a closed craniocerebral injury.

2. The evidence we received from the autopsy:

[left 100]
a) multiple bruisers and hemorrhages in the soft tissue, caused by multiple blunt force corpus and limbs trauma.

b) both his ears are swollen and purple, his lips are split, his nose is broken, there are scratches and hematomas on his hands and fingers, and there are bruises on his arms, back, tibia and knees.

[left 50]
3. In terms of the injuries sustained, it is concluded that the victim was subjected to battery with serious trauma which led to death.

[left 0, align right]
Pathologist S.Perlmutter