HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Executive Chief J.Dekker

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Report of an incident on 26th of September

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", align left, height 18, indent 25]
In the evening of 26th of September the HD512 item, maintained by the private zone, tried to escape from the barracks section. It immobilized the staff at gunpoint, blew up the wall of the sanitary area with the help of an I.E.D. and broke into technical tunnels where it faced security bots. 

The high power switchboard No.124 was damaged in the crossfire and it led to its detonation and a partial collapse of the structure.


The result is:

[indent 0, left 50]
1. Equipment in 3 rooms of the engineering section was damaged.

2. 12 security bots were put out of service.

3. Technical tunnels No.17 and No.42 were blocked.

4. Infrastructure is damaged.

5. Chief Migration Engineer Wolf was in the south corridor at the moment of the collapse and was killed under the rubble. In place of the deceased engineer Wolf, his trainee engineer Skinner was appointed.


[indent 25, left 0]
The circumstances of the escape are under investigation by detective Jensen now.

Overall damage is being estimated.

As the equipment and infrastructure were damaged, production delays up to 7 days are possible.

[align right]
Technical Chief I.Freeman