HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Hazard level raising order 

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Due to Worthington’s delivery group's death, and high risk of the facility being attacked, I command:

[indent 0, left 50]
1. To raise hazard level up to 3rd.
2. To enact additional bots for patrolling.
3. To increase the inspection of all the arriving and departing shuttles.
4. To strengthen the objects supervision.

[left 0, align right]
Security Chief M.Taggart