HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Security Chief M.Taggart

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Explanatory memorandum

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
During my last shift engineer Strauss’s colleagues visited him to solve some work issues. 

In the course of the visit there was a struggle during which the accused was inflicted injuries incompatible with life. He passed away before the arrival of the emergency.

I consider myself innocent, as in a condition of a high hazard level I couldn’t keep an eye on the cell, so I completely trusted the staff.

[left 0, align right, indent 0]
Bullpen duty officer, Private Clayton