HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align right]
To Security Chief M.Taggart

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Investigation report

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
During the investigation it was found that it is Dr. Dorian who was responsible for the theft of medical supplies from storage.

In the course of the attempted arrest, Dorian threw medical liquid in officer Dent’s face and, having obtained his sidearm, opened fire. 

Trying to escape, Dorian locked himself in a utility room of the medical sector. The decision to breach the wall through the medical locker room was made to neutralize him. But Dorian had been dead by the moment of break-in.

Having been affected by medication and stress, he wasn’t able to control his acts and tried to escape through the vent by blocking the fan with a crowbar. He didn't manage to block it in an appropriate way and as a result suffered fatal injuries. 

[left 0, align right]
The investigation is completed.
Detective A.Jensen