HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Message from Security Chief M.Taggart 

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
And again I’ve got a complaint against you having fun at the gallery. Any more tricks like that, and I’ll personally come down, get you into poses as twisted as possible and shove all the things found in the mannequins up your b-holes.