HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Russo_one.ttf", height 20, align center]
Message from Security Chief M.Taggart

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
I heard a rumor that some people on duty don’t like that folks from all over the facility visit the gym, passing their checkpoint.

I’ve got a great idea to move the gym to the residential area.

So you stop complaining, or cross someone else’s checkpoints.