HD_TEXT

[font "System\\Verdana.ttf", height 18, align left, indent 25]
Kane, situation update.

Comms array was damaged by the explosion. Two operbots locked themselves in the arsenal, still no luck to flush them out. One operbot was seen at the engineering. Surveillance is limited, as half of the cameras are not responding. The facility is in panic.

Casualties: control room staff, 4 people on duty, a few engineers. Two dozens wounded.

The whereabouts of the delivery group Commander are yet unknown.